<resources>
    <string name="app_name">New2</string>
    <!--                      Chia Lei                           -->
    <!-- welcome -->
    <string name="WelcomeText1">Welcome to FITFIT apps</string>
    <string name="WelcomeText2">Plan your workout and start healthy from now.</string>

    <string name="LoginGoogleEmail">Login with Google Email</string>
    <string name="LoginFb">Login with Facebook</string>
    <string name="LoginInsta">Login with Instagram</string>

    <!-- sign up -->
    <string name="SignUp">Sign Up</string>

    <string name="signupText1">Already an user? Login</string>

    <!-- login -->
    <string name="Login">Login</string>

    <string name="registerText1">Not register yet? Sign Up</string>

    <!-- bottom -->
    <string name="home">Home</string>
    <string name="workout">Workout</string>
    <string name="add_record">Add Record</string>
    <string name="chart">Chart</string>
    <string name="profile">Profile</string>

    <!-- home -->
    <string name="meal_plan">Meal Plan</string>
    <string name="meal_plan_desc">Meal Plan Description</string>

    <!-- home meal plan detail-->
    <string name="homeDescription1">If doesn\'t Challenge you</string>
    <string name="homeDescription2">It doesn\'t Change you</string>
    <string name="mealPlan">Meal Plan</string>
    <string name="workoutPlan">Workout Plan</string>
    <string name="weight_lossPlan">Weight Loss Plan</string>
    <string name="nutritionKnowledge">Nutrition Knowledge</string>
    <string name="activityPlan">Activity Plan</string>

    <string name="meal_plan_title">Meal Plan Title</string>
    <string name="meal_plan_detail_desc">Meal Plan Description</string>

    <string name="keep_fit_plan">
        A meal plan to keep fit typically focuses on providing your body with the right balance of
        nutrients, including lean protein, complex carbohydrates, healthy fats, and a variety of
        fruits and vegetables. Additionally, it\'s important to control portion sizes and stay
        hydrated. Here\'s a sample meal plan for a day:\n\n

        Breakfast:\n
        •Oatmeal with berries and a sprinkle of nuts or seeds\n
        •A glass of water or herbal tea\n\n

        Mid-Morning Snack:\n
        •Greek yogurt with honey and a handful of mixed nuts\n
        •A piece of fruit, such as an apple or a banana\n\n

        Lunch:\n
        •Grilled chicken breast or tofu salad with a variety of colorful vegetables
        (spinach, bell peppers, cucumbers, cherry tomatoes)\n
        •A vinaigrette dressing made with olive oil and balsamic vinegar\n
        •Quinoa or brown rice on the side\n\n

        Afternoon Snack:\n
        •Carrot and celery sticks with hummus\n
        •A small portion of cottage cheese or a boiled egg\n\n

        Dinner:\n
        •Baked or grilled salmon or a vegetarian protein source like lentils or chickpeas\n
        •Steamed broccoli, cauliflower, and carrots\n
        •A small serving of whole-grain pasta or brown rice\n\n

        Evening Snack (optional):\n
        •A handful of berries or a piece of dark chocolate (70% cocoa or higher)\n\n
        Hydration: Throughout the day, aim to drink plenty of water to stay hydrated.\n
        You can also enjoy herbal teas or infused water with slices of lemon, cucumber, or mint.\n\n

        Tips:\n
        •Try to keep your portion sizes moderate and avoid overeating.\n
        •Limit sugary and processed foods, as well as high-calorie snacks and drinks.\n
        •Choose lean sources of protein, such as poultry, fish, tofu, beans, and legumes.\n
        •Opt for whole grains over refined grains for added fiber and nutrients.\n
        •Incorporate a variety of fruits and vegetables to ensure you get a wide range of vitamins
        and minerals.\n\n\n
    </string>

    <string name="weight_loss_plan">
        Please note that this is a general example, and individual dietary needs may vary. Be sure to
        consult with a healthcare provider or registered dietitian before starting any weight loss plan.\n\n

        Day 1:\n
        Breakfast: Scrambled eggs with spinach and tomatoes.\n
        Snack: Greek yogurt with berries.\n
        Lunch: Grilled chicken breast with a side salad (lettuce, cucumber, and vinaigrette dressing).\n
        Snack: Carrot and celery sticks with hummus.\n
        Dinner: Baked salmon with steamed broccoli and quinoa.\n\n

        Day 2:\n
        Breakfast: Oatmeal with sliced banana and a teaspoon of honey.\n
        Snack: A small handful of almonds.\n
        Lunch: Turkey and avocado wrap with whole-grain tortilla.\n
        Snack: Sliced bell peppers with guacamole.\n
        Dinner: Stir-fried tofu with mixed vegetables and brown rice.\n\n

        Day 3:\n
        Breakfast: Greek yogurt parfait with granola and mixed berries.\n
        Snack: Apple slices with almond butter.\n
        Lunch: Lentil and vegetable soup with a side of mixed greens.\n
        Snack: Cottage cheese with pineapple.\n
        Dinner: Grilled shrimp with asparagus and quinoa.\n\n

        Day 4:\n
        Breakfast: Whole-grain toast with smashed avocado and poached eggs.\n
        Snack: A handful of walnuts.\n
        Lunch: Grilled vegetable and chickpea salad with balsamic dressing.\n
        Snack: Sliced cucumber with tzatziki sauce.\n
        Dinner: Baked chicken breast with roasted Brussels sprouts and sweet potato.\n\n

        Day 5:\n
        Breakfast: Smoothie with spinach, banana, and protein powder.\n
        Snack: Low-fat string cheese.\n
        Lunch: Quinoa salad with black beans, corn, and salsa.\n
        Snack: Cherry tomatoes with mozzarella cheese.\n
        Dinner: Baked cod with sautéed kale and brown rice.\n\n

        Day 6:\n
        Breakfast: Cottage cheese with sliced peaches and a drizzle of honey.\n
        Snack: Baby carrots with hummus.\n
        Lunch: Turkey and vegetable stir-fry with brown rice.\n
        Snack: A small handful of mixed nuts.\n
        Dinner: Grilled steak with roasted cauliflower and quinoa.\n\n

        Day 7:\n
        Breakfast: Whole-grain waffles with Greek yogurt and fresh strawberries.\n
        Snack: Sliced bell peppers with guacamole.\n
        Lunch: Spinach and feta stuffed chicken breast with a side of green beans.\n
        Snack: Sliced apple with a sprinkle of cinnamon.\n
        Dinner: Baked tilapia with asparagus and wild rice.\n\n

        Remember to stay hydrated throughout the day by drinking plenty of water or herbal tea. This
        meal plan emphasizes whole foods, lean protein sources, fruits, vegetables, and whole grains,
        which can support a balanced and healthy approach to weight loss. Adjust portion sizes to fit
        your specific calorie needs and dietary preferences.\n\n\n
    </string>

    <string name="muscle_building_plan">
        High-protein diets can help support muscle growth and repair. Please keep in mind that individual
        protein needs may vary, so adjust portion sizes and total daily protein intake based on your
        specific requirements and goals.\n\n

        Day 1:\n
        Breakfast: Scrambled eggs with spinach and tomatoes.\n
        Snack: Greek yogurt with a handful of almonds.\n
        Lunch: Grilled chicken breast with quinoa and mixed vegetables.\n
        Snack: Cottage cheese with pineapple chunks.\n
        Dinner: Baked salmon with steamed broccoli and brown rice.\n\n

        Day 2:\n
        Breakfast: Protein smoothie with whey protein powder, banana, and almond milk.\n
        Snack: Sliced cucumber with hummus.\n
        Lunch: Tuna salad (canned tuna, mixed greens, cherry tomatoes, and olive oil dressing).\n
        Snack: Hard-boiled eggs.\n
        Dinner: Lean beef stir-fry with broccoli and cauliflower rice.\n\n

        Day 3:\n
        Breakfast: Omelet with spinach, mushrooms, and feta cheese.\n
        Snack: Low-fat cottage cheese with sliced strawberries.\n
        Lunch: Grilled turkey burger with a side salad.\n
        Snack: Edamame (steamed young soybeans).\n
        Dinner: Baked cod with quinoa and asparagus.\n\n

        Day 4:\n
        Breakfast: Greek yogurt parfait with granola and mixed berries.\n
        Snack: Mixed nuts (almonds, walnuts, and cashews).\n
        Lunch: Chicken and vegetable kebabs with tzatziki sauce and whole-grain pita.\n
        Snack: Sliced bell peppers with guacamole.\n
        Dinner: Pork tenderloin with roasted Brussels sprouts and sweet potato.\n\n

        Day 5:\n
        Breakfast: Protein pancakes topped with sliced bananas and a drizzle of honey.\n
        Snack: Low-fat string cheese.\n
        Lunch: Beef and broccoli stir-fry with brown rice.\n
        Snack: Sliced apples with peanut butter.\n
        Dinner: Grilled shrimp with quinoa and sautéed kale.\n\n

        Day 6:\n
        Breakfast: Scrambled eggs with smoked salmon and dill.\n
        Snack: Celery sticks with almond butter.\n
        Lunch: Lentil and vegetable soup with a side of mixed greens.\n
        Snack: Greek yogurt with a drizzle of honey.\n
        Dinner: Baked chicken thighs with roasted asparagus and wild rice.\n\n

        Day 7:\n
        Breakfast: Spinach and mushroom frittata.\n
        Snack: Baby carrots with hummus.\n
        Lunch: Turkey and black bean salad with salsa dressing.\n
        Snack: Sliced cucumber with tzatziki sauce.\n
        Dinner: Baked tilapia with quinoa and steamed green beans.\n\n

        Remember to stay hydrated by drinking plenty of water throughout the day, as proper hydration
        is essential for muscle recovery and overall health. This meal plan emphasizes lean protein
        sources such as chicken, fish, lean beef, and dairy products to support muscle growth and repair.
        Adjust portion sizes and total daily protein intake as needed based on your specific dietary
        requirements and fitness goals.\n\n\n
    </string>

    <!-- add record -->
    <string name="recordDescription1">Work Out + Eat Well + Be Patient</string>
    <string name="recordDescription2">Your Body Will Reward You!!!</string>

    <string name="fitnessGoals">Fitness Goals</string>
    <string name="physicalActivity">Physical Activity</string>
    <string name="weight_body">Weight &amp; Body</string>
    <string name="waterIntake">Water Intake</string>
    <string name="caloriesBurned">Calories Burned</string>
    <string name="dietaryIntake">Dietary Intake</string>
    <string name="sleepPatterns">Sleep Patterns</string>
    <string name="heartRate_bloodPressure">Blood Pressure</string>
    <string name="userName">User</string>
    <string name="email">user@gmail.com</string>

    !-- profile -->
    <string name="goals">Goals</string>
    <string name="feedback">Feedback</string>
    <!-- fragment -->
    <string name="notification">Notification</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <!--                      Chia Lei                           -->
</resources>